http://www.maptools.com/policy

Our Policies
Our basic policy is that we want out customers to have quality mapping tools that meet their needs.
We do occasionally make mistakes and every now and then a product that doesn't meet our quality standards
slips out. Please let us know if there is a problem, we want to get it right.
Once your needs are met, we won't send you marketing emails to encourage you to buy more stuff.
We expect that as a satisfied customer you'll return when you next have a need for our products.
At MapTools.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect
about you to process orders, provide customer support, determine our sales tax obligations, and nothing else. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.
Privacy
What information do we collect? How do we use it?
Information You Provide
Shopping and Ordering
When you place an order or use our shopping cart, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, and the items you have added to your shopping cart.
This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order's status.
Payment Information
Your credit card information is transmitted directly from your web browser to our payment processor.
We never see your card number, and it is not stored on our server. The payment processor returns a token to us
that can only be used for a transaction between MapTools and your card account.
With that token we can authorize and complete a single charge, or refund all or part of that charge.
While quite secure, it can be a bit limiting as well. If you call or email us with a request to add an item to your order
or ship by a faster more costly method, we will need to get your card information again for the additional charge.
Communications
If you contact us by email, telephone, or fax, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number,
the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.
Information We Collect When You Use Our Services
Web Server Log Files
As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. In addition,
when you use our Services, we may collect certain information automatically from your device. This information may include internet protocol (IP)
addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, clickstream data, landing page, and referring URL.
Cookies
We use cookies to identify your web browsing session. This allows us to keep track of the items in your shopping cart, the details of any custom tools you are constructing,
and you login status if you are a registered user. If your web browser refuses to store our cookie, you will likely be unable to use our shopping cart to order products.
Visiting MapTools' website with your browser settings adjusted to accept cookies tells us that you want to use MapTools' products and
services, and that you consent to our use of cookies to provide them to you as described in this notice.
Unlike many other web sites, we do not use cookies for advertising, or to attempt to track other web sites that you visit.
We do not add any third party cookies for advertising, tracking, or analytical purposes.
What do we do with the Information we collect?
Primarily we use the information to process your order, and keep you informed about it. On rare occasions we have used the information to contact customers
that ordered a product that we later discovered had a problem they should be aware of. Occasionally we have sent an email about a new product to customers that
have made inqueries in the past about the avaialibility of a product like the new one.
Your Choices
Should you receive a promotional email from us in the future, we will provide a link to opt out of further promotional emails. Currently we are not sending promotional emails.
Many browsers have the option to disable, selectively enable, or remove cookies. Please note that, if you choose not to accept cookies, some features of our Services,
most notably the shopping cart, may no longer work for you.
Disclosure
We provide you name and shipping address to our shipping carriers when we determine the cost of shipping your order, and again when we purchase and print the shipping label. Currently we are using the services of EasyPost.com for this.
We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. The exception to that policy would be when we reasonably believe it is necessary to comply with a subpoena,
court order, law, or regulation. We may disclose your personal information to the extent required to fulfill our legal obligation.
Security
All personal information is collected via HTTPS secure communication and is kept in a secure database. We employ a variety of security technologies and measures
designed to protect information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. The measures we use are designed to provide a level of security appropriate
to the risk of processing your personal information. We work hard to keep up with current security practices.
There are only two of us here at MapTools, so we think it is unlikely that there will be a theft of data by an insider.
However, please bear in mind that the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure.
Data Retention
We retain personal information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example,
to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal, tax, or accounting requirements).
Access
You may request access to information associated with your orders by emailing me at john@maptools.com.
You may also request removal of the information associated with your orders by emailing me at john@maptools.com.
Business transfer
If MapTools is involved in a business acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, or bankruptcy
then your personal information may be transferred as part of the restructuring. I promise that either the acquiring
institution will respect your personal information and file data in accordance with this privacy policy,
or that you will be given the opportunity to opt-out of the transfer.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time. Changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on our website.
If we materially change the ways in which we use or share personal information previously collected from you through our Services,
we will notify you through our Services, by email, or other communication.
Returns and Refunds
We want you to have quality tools that are right for the task at hand.
If that's not what happened, we want to know. We'll gladly exchange tools so you get the right one.
We gladly issue a refund, if you just want to return your purchase. Often we will not even want you to
return the product. They just don't cost enough to get all worked up over returning a small plastic card,
and we'll just send you a replacement. For larger orders and more expensive items, we'll usually want
the product back. If it's our error that led to the problem we'll cover the return shipping. If the error
or change comes from your end, we would ask that you cover the return shipping.
We try to keep our policies short and simple. There is room for abuse, but thus far it's not been
a problem. We don't want to ever have to write pages of legalese which you have to "agree to" before ordering.
Please help us keep it that way by working with us to solve any problems you have. We're just people too.
And we're working hard doing what we love to do.
©Copyright 2020 MapTools All Rights Reserved
For more information please contact us
